<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Events on Decorah Knights</title>
    <link>https://decorahknights.org/events/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Events on Decorah Knights</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 16:07:41 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://decorahknights.org/events/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>FAITH &amp; DESSERT CATECHETICAL SERIES starting 23 August</title>
      <link>https://decorahknights.org/events/210823-faith-and-dessert/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Aug 2021 16:07:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://decorahknights.org/events/210823-faith-and-dessert/</guid>
      <description>FAITH &amp;amp; DESSERT SERIES
-WHAT IT&amp;rsquo;S ABOUT: The program will include dessert, adult-oriented catechesis (religious instruction), fellowship &amp;amp; conversation, and Benediction. -TOPIC FOR MONDAY 23 AUGUST 2021 PROGRAM: What&amp;rsquo;s the meaning of life? -WHEN &amp;amp; WHERE IT WILL TAKE PLACE: Will start Monday 23 August 2021 in Saint Benedict&amp;rsquo;s parish hall. It will run the 4th Monday of the following months @ 7 pm: August, September, October, January, February, March. Program will end each time @ 7:45 pm with Benediction; thus, this program will be short, SWEET (dessert!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eucharistic Adoration on 9 Aug 2021</title>
      <link>https://decorahknights.org/events/210809-eucharistic-adoration/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 16:00:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://decorahknights.org/events/210809-eucharistic-adoration/</guid>
      <description>Eucharistic adoration will occur on Monday 9 August 2021.
Hello Adorers,
Below are some possible intentions for your time in adoration. May the Lord work in and through your prayers.
For families who are overwhelmed by the pace of life and the responsibilities before them. For those discerning their vocation to married life, the priesthood, or the religious life. For our neighbors and neighborhood. &amp;ldquo;Dear Lord, Jesus Christ, in your precious name, I pray for the strengthening of the Catholic faith among my children and for the return to your blessed Church of all lapsed and non-practicing Catholics .</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Council Meeting on 9 Aug 2021</title>
      <link>https://decorahknights.org/events/210809-council-meeting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 15:00:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://decorahknights.org/events/210809-council-meeting/</guid>
      <description>Saint Benedict&amp;rsquo;s Council 4208 August meeting will take place on Monday 9 August 2021 @ 7 pm with a meal at 6:30.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
